Guide to the Ithaca and Tompkins County (N.Y.) printed material, 1858-1992.
Ithaca and Tompkins County (N.Y.) printed material, 1858-1992
- Series VII. Miscellaneous Materials
  - "The Neighborhood News,", Nov. 4, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Summer-Ithaca, 1961-1965 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Ithaca, New York: A General Plan, 1971 (Box 1)
  - Reminiscing Through Four Generations, 1841 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - By-Laws of the Ithaca Savings Bank, 1841 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - The Church Gazette, May 1, 1874 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Views of Ithaca, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Freeville Artesian Water Supply (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - "Ithaca Paints," an article in Life Magazine, Apr. 4, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Who's Who? (A Discussion About Anarchism), 1901 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Surroundings: Ithaca, NY-A Manual for Peripheral Streets Improvements, March 1978 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Stewart Park 1987 Preservation Goals and Guidelines (Box 3)
  - A History of the Railroads in Tompkins County, 1947 (Box 3)
  - "Dryden" by W. Franklin Moore, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - New and Living Styles and House Forms, May 13, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Community Renewal Program, June, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - McGraw House (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Ithaca Epidemic of 1903 (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous notes and correspondence from Mr. M. VanCleef, 1906 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - The Rise of Paris by Robert Ballanger, Jan. 21, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - The Flood of '72, Aug. 1972 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - 17th Annual United Way Report, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Hiring the Handicapped: Facts and Myths (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Homes: Warren Real Estate, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Town of Enfield directory, [1961] (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Free Hollow/Forest Home, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Enrollment of Voters, Tompkins County, First Assembly District [16 volumes], 1929-1953 (Box 4)
  - Ithaca Sign Company banner (Map-case Folder 1)
  - Calendar, 1974 (Map-case Folder 2)
  - Poster relating to Wharton Studios and the 75th anniversary of movie making in Ithaca, produced by Terry Harbin, 1990 (Map-case Folder 2)